* contract address: todo
* used libraries: Role librarie ==> to manage the different roles.
* IPFS: Not done. All frontend files (html, css, js ) could have been uploaded to IPFS so our website would have been decentralized also.
*  Solidity v0.4.19 (solc-js)
* node v10.18.0
* Truffle v4.1.0
* web3  v1.2.6

Remarks:
==> My project is almost finished but I encountered a problem that hinders me to finish it. I also have 2 questions: 

1. When I migrate my contracts to the network created by Ganache, all my contracts have the same owner: accounts[0]. So 
   address accounts[0] is also a farmer, retailer, consumer and distributor. All my other addresses are not used. This
   is not what I expected and it is troublesome because due to this I had to comment the modifiers onlyFarmer, onlyRetailer,
   onlyDistributor and onlyConsumer from my functions. Could you please tell me why my Role contracts are getting the 
   wrong owner ? I need to have this issue resolved before I can send the contracts to the testnet, which is why I didn't
   provide a contract address.

2. I also don't understand the purpose of contract Ownable. I think I don't need it which is why I didn't use it. 

3. When I use Ownable I get a conflict. Ownable has a function owner() but SupplyChain has an attribute owner. Because
   both names are the same, the compiler complains. As I am not using Ownable at the moment it doesn't matter that much,
   but maybe after you explain me point 2, I will need to add Ownable and then I will run against this issue. Should I 
   then change the name of the function from owner() to Owner() ? 